# Christopher Harrison

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### Career Profile

A full-stack software engineer with 7 years' experience in .NET, JavaScript frameworks, and SQL/NoSQL databases. Recognised for overcoming complex technical obstacles and implementing DevOps processes to improve software quality and reduce development cycle time. Expertise in mining and oil & gas industries, leading global teams, and managing stakeholder expectations.

# **Professional Experience**

Software Engineer 2016 – 2018

kanepi

A small software boutique specializing in process digitisation and data management in the oil and gas sector

- Designed and developed multiple web applications as a full-stack developer, utilising Microsoft SQL Server, SSRS Reporting, C#/ASP.NET, and the Knockout JavaScript framework
- Led several software projects involving business process digitisation and production reporting in the Oil & Gas industry
- Travelled domestically and internationally to assist with deployment, commissioning, and user training for various projects

Senior Software Engineer 2018 – 2022

Asset Maintenance Group

A specialized consultancy providing maintenance management services and custom developed software to domestic and international mining and manufacturing industries

- Developed an Excel-based application using VBA to assist with work order scheduling and reporting for multiple clients in the Mining industry across Australia
- Managed the design, development, and deployment of an improved work management software system, developed as a cross-platform .NET web application that integrated with enterprise systems to provide enhanced automation, data management, and reporting functionalities
- Used Azure DevOps to implement a CI/CD system to automate code quality control, software testing, and packaging

#### Senior Software Engineer / Team Lead

2022 - Ongoing

Rise-X

A fast-growing international company that enhances economic, social, and environmental outcomes for global businesses by transforming data and processes into the digital world

- Designed and implemented enhancements to the architecture of various cloud products to enable scaling from hundreds to millions of active users
- Integrated new QA/QC processes into existing Continuous Integration systems to improve code quality standards and encourage a culture of continuous improvement
- Exemplified high-quality Agile software development practices by frequently and consistently engaging with internal and external stakeholders to minimize project risk and maximize project outcomes
- Reduced development uncertainties and improved developer capabilities by implementing documentation procedures and ensuring that all team members gained a wide breadth of experience
- Currently leading a global team of engineers to develop a multi-party supply chain management system. Technologies include React, .NET, and a NoSQL data store.

#### Contact Me

- +61 410 035 144
- @ me@crh.dev
- in linkedin.com/in/crharrison
- Perth, Western Australia

## Education

BSc Engineering Science and Computer Science

2013 - 2015

University of Western Australia

# Frameworks/Platforms

ASP.NET Core, Node

React, Vue, Angular

MongoDB, MS SQL Server, GraphQL

Microsoft Azure, Digital Ocean, On-premises

## Hobbies/Interests

Embedded electronics design 3D printing, CNC machining Cyber security research

#### References

Available on request